

Contact

Phone: 8754288847

Email:

monikapanneer194@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/monika-p-5864b6164

Address:

No.107, Shrivven's Gokulam Apartment, Hagadur Main Road, Whitefield, Bangalore.

Key Skills

- · Content writing
- Social Media Calendar Creation
- Social Media Marketing
- Instagram, Facebook, LinkedIn, Youtube
- Google docs, Google Sheets
- Power Point Presentation
- Word Press
- Google Ads
- Canva
- Notion

Language

- English
- Tamil

Hobbies

- Drawing and Painting
- Making Crafts
- Playing Chess

Monika P

Social Media Manager

An enthusiastic person with creative mindset holding over 4 years of experience in creating, implementing and optimizing social media strategy for companies and brands. Relentlessly focused on generating new revenue through the use of social media.

Work Experience

October 2022 - Present.

Freelancing Social Media Content Writer.

- Worked with few brands for Social media content calendar, blogs, and website content.
- Brands worked: Sirpi Aesthetics <u>sirpicentre.com</u>, Aaraa & Livaa, Suga Goodness, Green Globe, and blogs for Alien Design studio.
- **O** June 2022 September 2022.

Thistle Media, Bangalore

Social Media Manager.

- **Brands worked:** Brahma Brews, Hakuna Matata, Nalapad Academy, Innate Splendore, Feybrush, Indian Paratha Company, Club VII.
- Designed Social media content calendar each month and executed on it on social media platforms.
- Optimized the content calendar across all platforms to coincide with new marketing and product launches.
- Understand the need of the client and bring out the output.
- Collaborate with designers to execute my vision into a good creative design.
- Develop, implement, and manage social media strategy to boost the sales and generated leads.
- Worked on competitor analysis for the brands to further understand target audience and goals based on social media trends.
- Boosted the engagement through my posts and reel creation and increased the followers count to 15% in a month.

O August 2020 - May 2022.

Makers Tribe, Chennai.

Social Media Marketing Executive

- Created few blogs for the company's website on topics like:
 - 1. Domains and Hosting. 2. My Experience in the IoT Workshop.
 - 3. Financial Planning for Life Goals. https://makerstribe.in/
- Provided marketing strategy for the company to increase the target audience.
- Helped in boosting the company's social media platforms to 50% in the estimated time.

O April 2019 - July 2020.

Sutherland Global Services. Chennai.

Customer Support Executive

- Worked with AT&T product.
- Resolve the issues of the customer through chat process.
- Worked closely with Technical support team in solving the issues.
- Got appreciation from the customers for resolving their issues.

Education

B.E, Civil Engineering (2014 - 2018), 7.2 CGPA

Vel Tech High Tech Dr. Rangarajan Dr. Sakunthala Engineering College, Chennai.

HSC, 92%

Sri Vijay Vidyalaya Matriculation Higher Secondary School, Dharmapuri.

SSLC, 94%

Sigaram Matriculation Higher Secondary School, Vaniyambadi.

Achievements

- School First in the SSLC Examination.
- Winner in Zonal level Chess competition under 13.
- Won prizes in English Essay Writing in school and college level.